Finding Aid for the George P. Johnson Negro Film Collection LSC.1042
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Research Files
  - S
    - Savage, Archie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 29; 310-311; 313. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 299, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 159; 558. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 485-7. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 670-672. (Reel 12)
    - The Savage Girl, Frame(s) 488, Floyd Shackleford. (Reel 11)
    - Savoy Ballroom
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 249, Cab Calloway. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 629-72, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
    - Sawyer, Ruth, Frame(s) 489; 856, Splendora Film Corporation. (Reel 11)
    - Saxon, Ruth, Frame(s) 490. (Reel 11)
    - Say it in French, Frame(s) 491, Billy Daniels. (Reel 11)
    - Scalphunters, The, Frame(s) 492-495. (Reel 11)
    - Scandal Street, Frame(s) 496, Louise Beavers. (Reel 11)
    - Scapegoat, Frame(s) 497. (Reel 11)
    - Scar of Shame
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 117, Colored Players Film Corporation. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 498. (Reel 11)
    - The Scarlet Hour, Frame(s) 499. (Reel 11)
    - Scattergood Baines, Frame(s) 500, Willie Best. (Reel 11)
    - Scent of Danger, Frame(s) 501. (Reel 11)
    - The Schemers, Frame(s) 502. (Reel 11)
    - Schomburg Collection, Frame(s) 443-523. (Reel 9)
    - Schuyler, George S., Frame(s) 495, on interracial marriages. (Reel 1)
    - Schuyler, Patricia, Frame(s) 500. (Reel 4)
    - Schwarze Blitz (Black Lightening), Frame(s) 503, Olive Moorefield. (Reel 11)
    - Scott, Bob, Frame(s) 504. (Reel 11)
    - Scott, Emmet
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 588-627, Birth of a Race Corporation. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 255-279, Robert Levy; 327-715 LPMC. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 505-15. (Reel 11)
    - Scott, Hazel, Frame(s) 516-39 * (Reel 11)
      (Note: Ms. Scott's films are listed alphabetically)
    - Scott, Henry
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 121-25, Anna Lucasta. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 48, One-Eyed Jacks. (Reel 10)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 540-43. (Reel 11)
    - Scott, Leslie, Frame(s) 544. (Reel 11)
    - Scott, Ray, Frame(s) 418, Barrel House Blues. (Reel 1)
    - Scott, Sylvester, Frame(s) 11-12; 545, Raintree County. (Reel 11)
    - Scott, Tom, Frame(s) 546-7. (Reel 11)
    - Scrivner, Calla, Frame(s) 308, Carribean Story. (Reel 2)
    - Scrivner, Calla
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 308, Carribean Story. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 548; 819. (Reel 11)
    - Seawife, Frame(s) 549. (Reel 11)
    - Seabrook, Joan, Frame(s) 352, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - Sears, Al, Frame(s) 519. (Reel 9)
    - Sebree, Charles, Frame(s) 299, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - Seconds, Frame(s) 550, Quincy Jones. (Reel 11)
    - Secret of Selling the Negro, Frame(s) 551, magazine article. (Reel 11)
    - Secret Sorrow, Frame(s) 552-554. (Reel 11)
    - Secret Witness, Frame(s) 555, Clarence Muse. (Reel 11)
    - Secrets of a Nurse, Frame(s) 556, Clarence Muse. (Reel 11)
    - See How They Run, Frame(s) 557, changed to Bright Road. (Reel 11)
    - Sekka, Johnny
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 607-8. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 535. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 558. (Reel 11)
    - Semi-detached, Frame(s) 559, Frank Silvera. (Reel 11)
    - Senegalese, Frame(s) 560. (Reel 11)
    - Senza Peita, Frame(s) 561-4. (Reel 11)
    - Sepia Arts Pictures Company, Frame(s) 565. (Reel 11)
    - Sepia Cinderella
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 566, Billy Daniels. (Reel 11)
    - The Sergeant, Frame(s) 567, Memphis Slim. (Reel 11)
    - Sergeant Murphy, Frame(s) 568, Sam McDaniels. (Reel 11)
    - Sergeant Rutledge, Frame(s) 569-72. (Reel 11)
    - Sergeant Three, Frame(s) 573-77. (Reel 11)
    - Set My People Free, Frame(s) 578. (Reel 11)
    - The Seven File, Frame(s) 579. (Reel 11)
    - Seven-Mile Square, The, Frame(s) 580, Harry Belafonte. (Reel 11)
    - Seven Women, Frame(s) 581, Woody Strode. (Reel 11)
    - Seventy Times Seven, Frame(s) 582. (Reel 11)
    - Sex & the Single Girl, Frame(s) 583. (Reel 11)
    - Schackleford, Lloyd, Frame(s) 584-87 * (Reel 11)
      (Note: Mr. Schackleford's films are listed alphabetically)
    - Shadow of the Thin Man, Frame(s) 588, Louise Beavers. (Reel 11)
    - Shadowed by the Devil, Frame(s) 10, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Shadows, Frame(s) 589. (Reel 11)
    - Shaft
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 289, Moses Gunn. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 590. (Reel 11)
    - Shake, Rattle & Roll, Frame(s) 591. (Reel 11)
    - Shakespeare in Harlem, Frame(s) 590-661, Negroes in theatre. (Reel 9)
    - Shalako, Frame(s) 592. (Reel 11)
    - The Shamrock Handicap, Frame(s) 593, Eli Reynolds. (Reel 11)
    - Shannon, Alex K., Frame(s) 381-2, Easy Money. (Reel 4)
    - Shannon, J., Frame(s) 387, death. (Reel 9)
    - Shaw, Arvell, Frame(s) 538, High Society. (Reel 5)
    - Shawn, Shirley
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 60. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 594. (Reel 11)
    - She, Frame(s) 595, Noble Johnson. (Reel 11)
    - She Wore a Yellow Ribbon, Frame(s) 596, Noble Johnson. (Reel 11)
    - Sheer Luck, Frame(s) 597, Oscar Smith. (Reel 11)
    - Sheffield, Maceo
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Argus Pictures. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 399, Harlem on the Prairie. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 598. (Reel 11)
    - Shields, Frank, Frame(s) 9, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Shenandoah, Frame(s) 599-603. (Reel 11)
    - Sherrill, Joya, Frame(s) 508, Negro entertainers; 472. (Reel 4)
    - She's For Me, Frame(s) 604, Mantan Moreland. (Reel 11)
    - Shindig, Frame(s) 605. (Reel 11)
    - Shining Hour, Frame(s) 606, Hattie McDaniels. (Reel 11)
    - The Shirelles
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 182-3. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 607. (Reel 11)
    - Shock Corridor, Frame(s) 608. (Reel 11)
    - The Shopworn Angel, Frame(s) 609, Hattie McDaniels. (Reel 11)
    - The Short Cut, Frame(s) 610-11. (Reel 11)
    - A Shot in the Night, Frame(s) 612. (Reel 11)
    - Show Boat
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 192. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 613-21. (Reel 11)
    - Shuffle Along
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 590, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 323-4. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 910, William Grant Still. (Reel 11)
    - Shuford, Abbie, Frame(s) 622-5. (Reel 11)
    - Shut My Big Mouth, Frame(s) 626, Noble Johnson. (Reel 11)
    - Sibley & Epps, Frame(s) 629-72, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
    - Sides, Pat
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 283. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 627. (Reel 11)
    - Sidney, P.J.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 644-8. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 628. (Reel 11)
    - Sidodel Film Company, Frame(s) 629. (Reel 11)
    - Sign of the Cross, Frame(s) 630, Rex Ingram. (Reel 11)
    - Sign of the Wolf, Frame(s) 631. (Reel 11)
    - Sigrid & the Sergeant, Frame(s) 632. (Reel 11)
    - Siki, Reginald
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 30, KIng of Kings. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 633-4. (Reel 11)
    - The Silencer, Frame(s) 635. (Reel 11)
    - Silent Thunder, Frame(s) 637, James Edwards. (Reel 11)
    - Silver Chalice, Frame(s) 636. (Reel 11)
    - Silver Devil, Frame(s) 638. (Reel 11)
    - Silver, Horace, Frame(s) 600, Nat King Cole. (Reel 2)
    - Silver Spurs, Frame(s) 639, Charles Wilson. (Reel 11)
    - Silvera, Frank A.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 363-5, Julien Mayfield. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 640-59. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 100 (Reel 12)
        (Note: Mr. Silvera's films are listed alphabetically)
    - Simba, Frame(s) 660-3. (Reel 11)
    - Simms, Hilda
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 77; 124; 665. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 30-90, Joe Louis. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 628, Sidney, P.J.; 664-72. (Reel 11)
    - Simon Bolviar, Frame(s) 673, Raymond St. Jacque. (Reel 11)
    - Simone, Nina, Frame(s) 674-8. (Reel 11)
    - The Simp, Frame(s) 679. (Reel 11)
    - Simpkins, Arthur Lee, Frame(s) 58; 680. (Reel 11)
    - Simply Heavenly
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 209-18, Claudia McNeil. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 681. (Reel 11)
    - Simpson, Walter, Frame(s) 111-114, Andlauer Producers. (Reel 1)
    - Singing Kid, Frame(s) 682, Cab Calloway. (Reel 11)
    - Singing Nun, Frame(s) 683. (Reel 11)
    - Singleton, Zuttie, Frame(s) 684, Stormy Weather. (Reel 11)
    - Sinha Moca, Frame(s) 685. (Reel 11)
    - Sins of Rachel Cade, Frame(s) 686-8. (Reel 11)
    - Sir Lancelot, Frame(s) 689. (Reel 11)
    - Siren of the Tropics, Frame(s) 690. (Reel 11)
    - Sissle, Cynthia, Frame(s) 691. (Reel 11)
    - Sissle, Noble
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 667, Eubie Blake. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 204, Ralph Bunche. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 502; 629-72, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 691-699; 856, Splendor Film Corporation. (Reel 11)
    - Ski Party, Frame(s) 700. (Reel 11)
    - Skidoo, Frame(s) 701. (Reel 11)
    - Skillet, Bug-Eyed, Frame(s) 343. (Reel 5)
    - Skinner, Herbert, Frame(s) 464-7. (Reel 2)
    - Skirts Ahoy, Frame(s) 702. (Reel 11)
    - Sky Dragon, Frame(s) 703, Suzette Harbin. (Reel 11)
    - The Slacker, Frame(s) 704. (Reel 11)
    - Slator, Mark, Frame(s) 557, His Great Chance. (Reel 5)
    - Slaughter, Charles
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 705, death. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 412, Two in the Bed. (Reel 12)
    - Slaughter, Vernon, Frame(s) 706, Crowning Experience. (Reel 11)
    - The Slave, Frame(s) 707. (Reel 11)
    - Slave Mutiny, Frame(s) 708. (Reel 11)
    - Slave Ship, Frame(s) 709-10. (Reel 11)
    - Slaves, Frame(s) 710. (Reel 11)
    - Sledge, Percy, Frame(s) 499; 513. (Reel 4)
    - Sleep My Love, Frame(s) 711, Hazel Brooks. (Reel 11)
    - The Slender Thread (Call Me Back)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 245. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 712-5. (Reel 11)
    - Slim, Memphis, Frame(s) 567. (Reel 11)
    - Small Town Boy, Frame(s) 717, Clarence Wilson. (Reel 11)
    - Small Town Girl, Frame(s) 716, Nat King Cole. (Reel 11)
    - Smalley, Jim, Frame(s) 718. (Reel 11)
    - Small's Paradise, Frame(s) 145. (Reel 1)
    - Smart, Bobby, Frame(s) 557. (Reel 5)
    - Smile, Frame(s) 9, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Smiling Ghost, Frame(s) 719, Willie Best. (Reel 11)
    - Smiling Hate, Frame(s) 720. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Ada (Bricktop)
      See Ade DuConge
    - Smith, Alma
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 394. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 716, Lincoln Motion Picture Company. (Reel 7)
    - Smith, Bernice, Frame(s) 721. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Bessie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 194, Louis Armstrong; 690, Della Reese. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 414-29, Ray Charles. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 538. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 433, The Blues. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 722. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Connie, Frame(s) 154-5. (Reel 4)
    - Smith, Earl
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 2, Abandoned. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 387, death. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 723. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Ed
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 229, Crisis in the South. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 724. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Eddie, Frame(s) 437. (Reel 1)
    - Smith, Elwood
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 26, Boy, What a Girl. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
    - Smith, Ernest, Frame(s) 569, The Big City. (Reel 1)
    - Smith, Ethel
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 117, Colored Players Film Corporation. (Reel 3)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 392-562, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
    - Smith, Grace
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 488, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 725, The Millionaire. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Gus, Frame(s) 154. (Reel 4)
    - Smith, Henry
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 726, Louisiana. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 163-5, The $10,000 Trail. (Reel 12)
    - Smith, Homer, Frame(s) 727-31. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, James R., Frame(s) 732-752, collection of news on Black entertainers. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Jeli, Frame(s) 394, Harlem is Heaven. (Reel 5)
    - Smith, Jimmie (Actor), Frame(s) 710-5. (Reel 7)
    - Smith, Jimmie (Musician)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 184. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 406-29, Ray Charles. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 75, Swingin' Set. (Reel 12)
    - Smith, Leo, Frame(s) 753, Continental Film. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Leon, Frame(s) 159, The Intruder. (Reel 6)
    - Smith, Leonard, Frame(s) 754. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Mamie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 689. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 359. (Reel 8)
    - Smith, Mildred Joanne, Frame(s) 755, No Way Out. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Muriel
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 394. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 6; 756-767 *. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, N. Clark, Frame(s) 669, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
    - Smith, Norris
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 154-5. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 768-71. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Oscar
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 139, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 772-76 *. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Roy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 676, Blood & Sand. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 777. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, T.D.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 30, King of Kings. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 778, 10 Commandments. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Tommie, Frame(s) 779. (Reel 11)
    - Smith, Vivian, Frame(s) 469-75, Hearts in Dixie. (Reel 5)
    - Smoke Lightning, Frame(s) 780, Clarence Wilson. (Reel 11)
    - Smoking Guns, Frame(s) 781. (Reel 11)
    - Smythe, Mabel Sanford Lewis, Frame(s) 514, Negro entertainers. (Reel 4)
    - Snelson, Gertrude, Frame(s) 392-562, Oscar Micheaux. (Reel 8)
    - Snow, Valaida, Frame(s) 302. (Reel 9)
    - Snowball (Curtis McHenry)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 733-6, L-KO Motion Pictures. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 154. (Reel 8)
    - Snowden, Carol
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 111, In Old Kentucky. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 312, Marriage Clause. (Reel 8)
    - Snowden, Carolyn, Frame(s) 782-88. (Reel 11)
    - Snyder, Ed. L.
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 9, Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 789. (Reel 11)
    - Snyder, Gladys, Frame(s) 80, Gang War. (Reel 5)
    - So Dear To My Heart, Frame(s) 790, Jeremaih Kincaid. (Reel 11)
    - So Ends The Night, Frame(s) 791. (Reel 11)
    - So Red The Rose, Frame(s) 492. (Reel 11)
    - Sodom & Gomorrah, Frame(s) 793. (Reel 11)
    - Soft Cushions, Frame(s) 794. (Reel 11)
    - Soft Talk Me Home, Frame(s) 795. (Reel 11)
    - Soldier in the Rain, Frame(s) 796, Mimi Dillard. (Reel 11)
    - Soloman & Sheba, Frame(s) 797. (Reel 11)
    - Some Like It Hot, Frame(s) 798, Clarence Wilson. (Reel 11)
    - Someone to Love, Frame(s) 799, Oscar Smith. (Reel 11)
    - Something Always Happens, Frame(s) 800- 3. (Reel 11)
    - Something of Value, Frame(s) 804-11. (Reel 11)
    - Something to Shout About, Frame(s) 812, Hazel Scott. (Reel 11)
    - Somewhere in the World, Frame(s) 813. (Reel 11)
    - Son of Ingagi
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 227, Jessie Graves; 583, Hollywood Productions. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 814. (Reel 11)
    - Son of Satan, Frame(s) 815. (Reel 11)
    - Son of Sinbad, Frame(s) 816. (Reel 11)
    - A Song is Born, Frame(s) 817. (Reel 11)
    - Song of Freedom
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 18, Robert Adams. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 818, Paul Robeson. (Reel 11)
    - Song of Haiti, Frame(s) 819, Calla Scrivner. (Reel 11)
    - Song of the South
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 558. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 820. (Reel 11)
    - Sonic Film Production Company, Frame(s) 821. (Reel 11)
    - So's Your Uncle, Frame(s) 822, Delta Rhythm Boys. (Reel 11)
    - Sound of Fury
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 823-5. (Reel 11)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 288, Bill Gunn. (Reel 5)
    - South of Caliente, Frame(s) 826, Willie Best. (Reel 11)
    - South of Panama, Frame(s) 827, Sam McDaniels. (Reel 11)
    - South Pacific, Frame(s) 828-835. (Reel 11)
    - South to Karanga, Frame(s) 836, Ben Carter. (Reel 11)
    - Southern Negro, Frame(s) 838. (Reel 11)
    - Southern, Tom
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Argus Pictures. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 400, Harlem Rides the Range. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 837. (Reel 11)
    - Southland Pictures, Frame(s) 839. (Reel 11)
    - Southwest to Sonora, Frame(s) 840. (Reel 11)
    - Soyinka, Wole
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 410, 412. (Reel 9)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 841. (Reel 11)
    - Sparkes, Duke, Frame(s) 234, If I Should Die. (Reel 3)
    - Sparkes, Fay, Frame(s) 842, Sapphire. (Reel 11)
    - Sparrows Can't Sing, Frame(s) 844. (Reel 11)
    - Spartacus, Frame(s) 845-6, Woody Strode. (Reel 11)
    - Spearman, Rawa, Frame(s) 267. (Reel 1)
    - Special Man in Special Market, Frame(s) 647. (Reel 11)
    - The Spectrum, Frame(s) 848-851. (Reel 11)
    - Spectrum Arts, Incorporated, Frame(s) 851. (Reel 11)
    - Spectrum Film Corporation, Frame(s) 107. (Reel 3)
    - Speights, Dorothy, Frame(s) 350, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - Spell, George
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 504. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 852. (Reel 11)
    - Spencer, Kenneth
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Cabin in the Sky. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 853-4. (Reel 11)
    - Spencer, Edith, Frame(s) 66. (Reel 2)
    - Spencer Mountain, Frame(s) 855, Barbara McNair. (Reel 11)
    - The Spider's Web, Frame(s) 857. (Reel 11)
    - Spinster, Frame(s) 858. (Reel 11)
    - Spirit of Youth, Frame(s) 859. (Reel 11)
    - Spitfire, Frame(s) 860. (Reel 11)
    - Spivey, Victoria
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 670, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 317-21, Hallelujah. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 862. (Reel 11)
    - Splendor, Frame(s) 861, Clarence Brooks. (Reel 11)
    - Splendora Film Corporation, Frame(s) 856. (Reel 11)
    - The Split, Frame(s) 863-4. (Reel 11)
    - Spooks Run Wild, Frame(s) 865, Sunshine Sammy. (Reel 11)
    - The Sport of the Gods
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 3, Robert Abrams. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 866-870, Paul Laurence Dunbar. (Reel 11)
    - Sporting Blood, Frame(s) 871. (Reel 11)
    - Sportraits in Ebony, Frame(s) 872. (Reel 11)
    - Spotlight, Frame(s) 873. (Reel 11)
    - Spring, Frame(s) 874. (Reel 11)
    - Sproul, Newt, Frame(s) 117, Ghost Hunt. (Reel 5)
    - Spy with the Cold Nose, Frame(s) 875, Eric Portman. (Reel 11)
    - Spying with the Spy, Frame(s) 876. (Reel 11)
    - Square Joe
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 272, Joe Jeannette. (Reel 6)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 877. (Reel 11)
    - Square Jungle, Frame(s) 878. (Reel 11)
    - Stage Door Canteen, Frame(s) 879, Ethel Waters. (Reel 11)
    - Stand-Up & Cheer, Frame(s) 880, Stepin Fetchit. (Reel 11)
    - Standifer, Glenn, Frame(s) 352, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - Stanton, Mary or Mayra
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 241, Astor Pictures. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 881, The Betrayal. (Reel 11)
    - Star for a Night, Frame(s) 882, Hattie McDaniels. (Reel 11)
    - A Star is Born, Frame(s) 883-4. (Reel 11)
    - Star Spangled Rhythm, Frame(s) 885, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 11)
    - Stars in My Crown, Frame(s) 886, Juano Hernandez. (Reel 11)
    - Staton, Dakota, Frame(s) 647-8, Sarah Vaughan. (Reel 12)
    - Steamboat Bend, Frame(s) 887, Stepin Fetchit. (Reel 11)
    - Steamboat Bill, Jr., Frame(s) 888. (Reel 11)
    - Steel Helmet, Frame(s) 889-91. (Reel 11)
    - Steele, Geraldine, Frame(s) 73-4, Reformation. (Reel 11)
    - Step Brothers, Four
      See The Four Step Brothers
    - Stepping Toes, Frame(s) 894. (Reel 11)
    - Sterman, Otto, Frame(s) 895-902. (Reel 11)
    - Stevens, Lonnie, Frame(s) 903. (Reel 11)
    - Stewart, Harrison, Frame(s) 628. (Reel 1)
    - Stewart, Nicodemus
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 236, Cabin in the Sky. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 551, False Faces. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 136, Gildersleeve's Ghost. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 906. (Reel 11)
    - Stewart, Slam (Leroy)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 26, Boy, What a Girl. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 68-72, Slim Gailliard; 511, Herald Pictures. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 904. (Reel 11)
    - Stewart, Samuel, Frame(s) 905, Thunderbolt. (Reel 11)
    - Still, William Grant
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 509. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 907-1016. (Reel 11)
    - Stokes, Al, Frame(s) 253, Green Pastures. (Reel 5)
    - Stop the World, I Want to Get Off, Frame(s) 1. (Reel 12)
    - Storell, Viola, Frame(s) 2, Legion of Condemned. (Reel 12)
    - Stormy Weather, Frame(s) 3. (Reel 12)
    - Story of a 3-Day Pass
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 308. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 4. (Reel 12)
    - Story of the Sea Wife, Frame(s) 5. (Reel 12)
    - Story of Temple Drake, Frame(s) 6, Hattie McDaniels. (Reel 12)
    - Straight to Heaven, Frame(s) 7. (Reel 12)
    - Strange Harvest, Frame(s) 8, Hazel Scott. (Reel 12)
    - Strange Victory, Frame(s) 9. (Reel 12)
    - Stranger on the Run, Frame(s) 10, Bernie Hamilton. (Reel 12)
    - Strangers in Love, Frame(s) 11, Gertrude Howard. (Reel 12)
    - The Strangler, Frame(s) 12, Mimi Dillard. (Reel 12)
    - Strayhorn, Billy
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 184. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 449-89, Duke Ellington. (Reel 4)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 13. (Reel 12)
    - The Street, Frame(s) 14. (Reel 12)
    - Street of Women, Frame(s) 15, Louise Beavers. (Reel 12)
    - The Street That Never Slept, Frame(s) 95, book by Arnold Shaw. (Reel 3)
    - Strictly Personal, Frame(s) 16, Hazel Jones. (Reel 12)
    - The Strip, Frame(s) 17, Louis Armstrong. (Reel 12)
    - Strode, Woody, Frame(s) 18-43 *. (Reel 12)
    - Strozier, Othella, Frame(s) 300, Katherine Dunham. (Reel 4)
    - The Struggle, Frame(s) 198-202, Cosmolitan Picture Corporation. (Reel 3)
    - Stubbs, Louise, Frame(s) 44, Sweet, Love Bitter. (Reel 12)
    - Studio Film Incorporated, Frame(s) 45. (Reel 12)
    - Sublett, John W.
      See Buck 'n Bubbles
    - Submarine Command, Frame(s) 46. (Reel 12)
    - A Successful Failure, Frame(s) 47, Clarence Wilson. (Reel 12)
    - Sullivan, Maxine, Frame(s) 95. (Reel 3)
    - Sultewan, Naomi, Frame(s) 110, In Old Chicago. (Reel 6)
    - Sun Shine Bright, Frame(s) 48, Stepin Fetchit. (Reel 12)
    - Sundown, Frame(s) 49. (Reel 12)
    - Sunny Side of the Street, Frame(s) 50, Billy Daniels. (Reel 12)
    - Sunrise at Campobello, Frame(s) 51, Otis Greene. (Reel 12)
    - Sunset Cafe
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 249, Cab Calloway. (Reel 2)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 629-72, Footlite Magazine. (Reel 4)
    - Sunshine Sammy (Frederick Ernest Morrison)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 553, Berry Brothers. (Reel 1)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 556. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 325-715, LMP C. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 716-23 *. (Reel 8)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) Motion Picture Industry. (Reel 9)
    - Super Sleuth, Frame(s) 52, Willie Best. (Reel 12)
    - Super Speed, Frame(s) 53. (Reel 12)
    - Supreme Art Productions, Frame(s) 54. (Reel 12)
    - The Supremes
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 370, The Happening. (Reel 5)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 55-7. (Reel 12)
    - Sutton, Susie
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 167, The Brute. (Reel 7)
      - unspecified, Frame(s) 58. (Reel 12)
    - Swan, J.A., Frame(s) 59, Ain't She Sweet. (Reel 12)
    - Swanee River, 1929; Frame(s) 60. (Reel 12)
    - Swanee River, 1939; Frame(s) 61. (Reel 12)
    - Sweet Bird of Youth, Frame(s) 62. (Reel 12)